Finding aid for the Jerry Lewis papers LSC.2124
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 2: Election Campaigns, 1968-2010
  - Subseries 2.3: United States Congress, 1970-2010
    - 1978 Election: Endorsements of Lewis: Pettis, Shirley: Letters, Press (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - 1978 Election: Endorsements of Lewis: Reagan, Ronald: Letter, circa 1978 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - 1978 Election: Endorsements of Lewis: Reagan, Ronald: Richard Viguerie Letter Drafts, 1978 August (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - 1978 Election: Federal Election Commission Record Newsletter, 1978 May-August (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - 1978 Election: Finances: Budget, Primary and General Elections, 1978 March (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - 1978 Election: Finances: Campaign Reporting Reference Materials, 1978-1979 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - 1978 Election: Fundraiser Event: Anderholt, John: Thank-you Letters, 1978 April (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - 1978 Election: Fundraiser Event: Palm Springs, California, 1978 April 15 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - 1978 Election: Fundraiser Event: Salute for a Decade of Service; Redlands, California, 1978 October 25 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - 1978 Election: Fundraiser Event: San Bernardino, California, 1978 September 28 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - 1978 Election: Fundraiser Event: Victorville, California, 1978 March 31 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - 1978 Election: Fundraiser Event: Victorville, California, 1978 May 12 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - 1978 Election: Lewis for Congress Committee: Volunteer Forms, 1978 July (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - 1978 Election: Maps, 37th Congressional District, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - 1978 Election: National Republican Congressional Committee: Campaign Research, 1978 February-May (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - 1978 Election: National Republican Congressional Committee: Campaign Tips Newsletter, 1977 May-October (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - 1978 Election: Press Statements, 1978 January-September (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - 1978 Election: Student Voter Statistics, University of California System, 1978 April 4 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - 1978 Election: Voter Service Coalition: Request for Debate, 1978 October 20 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - 1978 Election: Zipcodes, 37th Congressional District, circa 1978 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - 1980 Election: Certificate of Election, General Election, 1980 December (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - 1980 Election: Finances: Campaign Contributions, 1980 October (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - 1980 Election: Finances: Campiagn Contributions Thank-you Letters, 1980 November 7 (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - 1980 Election: Fundraiser Event: Birthday Salute; San Bernardino, California, 1980 October 21 (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - 1980 Election: Fundraiser Event: Palm Springs, California, 1980 October 22 (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - 1980 Election: Fundraiser Event: Redlands, California (1 of 2), 1980 May 31 (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - 1980 Election: Fundraiser Event: Redlands, California (2 of 2), 1980 May 31 (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - 1980 Election: Fundraiser Event: Victorville, California, 1980 November 3 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - 1980 Election: Press Conference: Guest List and Mailgram, 1980 February 20 (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - 1982 Election: California Republican Assembly: Candidate Mailer for Republican Voters, 1981-1982 (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - 1982 Election: Fundraiser Event: Rancho Cucamunga, California, 1982 February 18 (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - 1982 Election: Fundraiser Event: San Bernardino, California, 1982 August 24 (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - 1984 Election: Distribution Materials: Friends of Jerry Lewis Letter, 1984 May (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - 1984 Election: District Research: 35th Congressional District, 1982-1983 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - 1984 Election: Finances: Campaign Contributions, 1984 June (Box 16, Folder 46)
    - 1984 Election: Finances: Campaign Contributions, 1984 September 6 (Box 16, Folder 47)
    - 1984 Election: Fundraiser Event, 1984 May-July (Box 16, Folder 48)
    - 1984 Election: Fundraiser Event: Summer Games Gala; San Bernardino, California, 1984 July 19 (Box 16, Folder 49)
    - 1986 Election: Campaign Results Data and Research, 1986 November (Box 16, Folder 50)
    - 1988 Election: Certificate of Nomination, Primary Election, 1988 July 1 (Box 16, Folder 51)
    - 1988 Election: Election Results and Voter Demographics (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - 1988 Election: Endorsements of Lewis, 1988 February-May (Box 16, Folder 52)
    - 1988 Election: Fund Raiser Event, 1988 September 27 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - 1988 Election: United States Chamber of Commerce Special Report: "They Grade Congress", 1988 April 25 (Box 16, Folder 53)
    - 1990 Election: Certificate of Election, General Election, 1990 December 14 (Box 16, Folder 54)
    - 1990 Election: Election Results and Voter Demographics, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - 1990 Election: Fundraiser Event, 1990 March 27 (Box 16, Folder 55)
    - 1990 Election: Fundraiser Event: Riverside, California, 1990 February-April (Box 16, Folder 56)
    - 1992 Election: California Republican Party: Election Coverage Newsletter, 1991 August-October (Box 16, Folder 57)
    - 1992 Election: Distribution Materials: Mailer, Absentee Ballot Information, 1992 October (Box 16, Folder 58)
    - 1992 Election: Reapportionment, Redistricting: Electoral Vote Analysis, Maps, Press Coverage, 1991 November-December (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - 1994 Election: Finances: Campaign Contributions, 1993 December (Box 16, Folder 59)
    - 1998 Election: Affidavit of Circulator, 1998 February (Box 16, Folder 60)
    - 1998 Election: California Republican Party: Campaign Calendar Manual, 1997 May 9 (Box 16, Folder 61)
    - 1998 Election: Distribution Materials: Mailers, circa 1997 (Box 16, Folder 62)
    - 2002 Election: Committee on Standards of Official Conduct: Campaign Activity Conduct Booklet, 2001 December (Box 16, Folder 63)
    - 2002 Election: Congratulations and Thank-you Letters (1 of 2), 2002 October-2003 January (Box 16, Folder 64)
    - 2002 Election: Congratulations and Thank-you Letters (2 of 2), 2002 October-2003 January (Box 16, Folder 65)
    - 2002 Election: Declaration of Candidacy, Nomination Paper, 2001 November (Box 16, Folder 66)
    - 2004 Election: Committee on Standards of Official Conduct: Memorandum, 2003 December 8 (Box 16, Folder 67)
    - 2008 Election: Campaign Opponent: Prince, Tim: Mailer, circa 2008 (Box 16, Folder 68)
    - 2008 Election: Distribution Materials: Mailers, circa 2008 (Box 16, Folder 69)
    - Distribution Materials: Bumper Stickers, circa 1977-2010 (Box 16, Folder 70)
    - Bag of Campaign Buttons, 1979-2012 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Subseries 2.4: Other Campaigns and Appointments, 1968-1993
    This small subseries contains records pertaining to the appointment of delegates, vicechairmen, and chairmen of the Republican State Central Committee. It also includes a variety of materials relating to national political races in which Jerry Lewis did not compete, but did support a candidate, such as Ronald Reagan's presidential run in 1976 and David Dreier's similarly ill-fated first run for California's 35th district in 1978.
    - Appointments: California Republican Party, 1975, 1975 January 14 (Box 16, Folder 71)
    - Appointments: California Republican Party, 1979-1980, 1979 January (Box 16, Folder 72)
    - Appointments: California Republican Party, 1981-1982, 1980 December-1981 January (Box 16, Folder 73)
    - Appointments: California Republican Party, 1983-1984, 1982 November-1983 October (Box 16, Folder 74)
    - Appointments: California Republican Party, 1985-1986, 1985 November-1987 January (Box 16, Folder 75)
    - Appointments: California Republican Party: 1987-1988, 1988-1989, 1987 January-1988 December (Box 16, Folder 76)
    - Appointments: California Republican Party, 1989-1990, 1988 December (Box 16, Folder 77)
    - Appointments: California Republican Party, 1991-1993, 1990 November-1991 February (Box 16, Folder 78)
    - Appointments: San Bernardino County Republican Party, Central Committee, 1982 January-April (Box 16, Folder 79)
    - Appointments: San Bernardino County Republican Party, Central Committee, 1993 January (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Appointments: Committee for the Survival of a Free Congress: Letters and Pamphlets, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Crane, David: Campaign for United States Congress, Indiana: Survey and Letter, circa 1978 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Dreier, David: Campaign for United States Congress, 35th District: Mailer, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Finch, Bob: Campaign for United States Senate: Distribution Materials, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Hansberger, Dennis: Campaign for California State Assembly, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Holden, Nate: Campaign for United States Congress, 28th District: Mailer, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Leonard, Bill: Campaign for California State Assembly: Lewis and Pettis Endorsements, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Lewis, John: Campaign for California State Assembly, 61st District, 1987-1988 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Lowery, Bill: Campaign for United States Congress, 50th District: Withdrawal Letter, 1992 April 28 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Perot, Ross: The First National Referendum, Government Reform: Ballot Results, 1993 April 14 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Pettis, Shirley; Congresswoman, 37th District: Letters, Press, 1968-1978 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Reagan, Ronald: Campaign for United States President, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Steiger, Sam: Campaign Contribution Request Letter, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Series 3: Legislative Files, 1969-2013
  This is the largest series of the collection. Included here are materials relating to legislation proposed or enacted during Lewis's ten years in the California State Assembly and his thirty-four years in the U.S. House of Representatives. This includes everything from the full text of bills to background information gleaned from public and private sources to correspondence with constituents and fellow politicians. The series is divided into three parts: legislation proposed or enacted by the State Assembly during Lewis's time in that body; congressional legislation which predominantly concerned the state of California in general and Lewis's districts in particular; and finally congressional legislation concerning topics which were mostly of national and international import.
  - Subseries 3.1: California State Assembly, 1969-1978
    This small subseries consists almost entirely of the full text of bills, amendments, and resolutions proposed and passed by the California State Assembly during Lewis's ten years as an assembly member. Some of this material focuses on legislation sponsored or co-sponsored by Lewis himself, but most does not. There are also a few folders which contain information on the Assembly as a whole and staff notes.
    - Bills, Amendments, and Resolutions, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Bills, Amendments, and Resolutions, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Bills, Amendments, and Resolutions, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Bills, Amendments, and Resolutions, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Framed Text of Assembly Bill 733 (1 page) with Picture of Jerry Lewis and Governor Ronald Reagan, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - California Assembly Member Book, 1971 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Bills, Amendments, and Resolutions, 1971-1972 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Bills, Amendments, and Resolutions, 1971-1972 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Bills, Amendments, and Resolutions, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Bills, Amendments, and Resolutions, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Bills, Amendments, and Resolutions, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Framed Text of Assembly Bill 792 (1 page) with Picture of Jerry Lewis, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Bills, Amendments, and Resolutions, 1973-1974 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Bills, Amendments, and Resolutions, 1973-1974 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Bills, Amendments, and Resolutions, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Bills, Amendments, and Resolutions, 1974-1976 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Bills, Amendments, and Resolutions, 1974-1976 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Bills, Amendments, and Resolutions, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Bills, Amendments, and Resolutions, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Bills, Amendments, and Resolutions, 1975-1976 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Framed Text of Assembly Bills 600, 601, and 3351 (1 page each), 1975-1976 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Bills, Amendments, and Resolutions, 1975-1976 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Lewis Legislation, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Lewis Legislation, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Lewis Legislation, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Bills, Amendments, and Resolutions, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Bills, Amendments, and Resolutions, 1976-1977 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Bills, Amendments, and Resolutions, 1976-1978 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Lewis Legislation, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Lewis Legislation, Press Shield Law (ACA), 1977 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Lewis Resolutions, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Staff Notes, 1977-1978 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Legislative Summaries, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Lewis Legislation, 1977-1978 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Bills, Amendments, and Resolutions, 1977-1978 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Legislative Handbook, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Lewis Legislative History, 1969-1978 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Bills, Amendments, and Resolutions, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Lewis Legislation 1969-1978 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Teamsters' Guidebook, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Subseries 3.2: US Congress, California Subject Files, 1979-2013
    The files in this subseries contain background information on issues that were important to Jerry Lewis because of their significance to California as a whole, or his district in particular. A number of these topics were also of national significance, but their inclusion in this subseries indicates that the underlying documents were primarily state or local in scope. The specific types of documents preserved include such things as newspaper clippings, publications, government reports, bill texts, and correspondence. The largest subjects are "Land, Water, and Energy," "Transportation," "Housing," "University Research," "Labor, HHS, Education," and "Public Health/Medicine." There are also a number of files arranged by locality (e.g., "San Bernardino," "Hesperia").
    - Agency Letters, 2011-2012 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Agriculture Conference, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Agricultural Leadership Program, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Agriculture Appropriations FY96, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Agriculture Appropriations FY97, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Agriculture Appropriations FY98, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Agriculture Appropriations FY01, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Agriculture Appropriations FY02, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Agriculture Appropriations, 2001-2003 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Grapes, Chilean Free Trade Agreement, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Apple Valley, GAVRT Telescope, 1999, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Apple Valley, Economic Development Administration Grant, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Appropriations, Mixed FY00–FY02, 1999-2001 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Appropriations, Mixed FY03, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Appropriations, Mixed, 2003-2007 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Appropriations, District Projects FY05, FY07, 2004-2006 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Appropriations, Mixed FY06, 2005 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Appropriations, Mixed FY07, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Appropriations, District Projects FY08–FY09, 2007-2008 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Appropriations, Project and Program Funding FY10, 2009 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Appropriations, Project and Program Funding FY11, 2010 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Appropriations Requests FY00, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Appropriations Requests FY01, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Appropriations Requests FY03, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Appropriations Requests FY04, FY06, 2003-2005 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Appropriations Requests FY08, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Barstow Sewage, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Beaumont Local Stimulus Projects, 2009-2011 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Big Bear Lake Civic Center, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Blythe, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Childhelp Village, 2008 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Colorado River Indian Tribes, 1976, 2004, 2008 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Commerce, Justice, State, Judiciary Subcommittee FY99, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Commerce, Justice, State, Judiciary Subcommittee FY00, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Commerce, Justice, State, Judiciary Subcommittee FY00, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Commerce, Justice, State, Judiciary Subcommittee FY99, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Defense: Barstow Veterans Home, 2000-2001 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Defense: Construction Appropriations FY08, 2007-2008 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Defense: Norton Air Force Base, 1997-1998 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Defense: Twentynine Palms Marine Base, 2007-2012 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Defense: Veterans Affairs, 1993-2000 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Delegation Letters, 1997-1998 (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - Delegation Letters, 1997-1998 (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - Earthquake Authority, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Earthquake Authority, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Earthquake Protection Act, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Economic Development Initiative Funding, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Fort Irwin, Twentynine Palms Appropriations, 1998-1999 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Fort Irwin, International Association of Machinists, 1994-1995 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Hesperia, Economic Development Administration Grant, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Hesperia Projects FY10, FY13, 2009-2013 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Housing: Casa Ramona, 2005 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Housing: Habitat for Humanity, Apple Valley, 1998-2001 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Housing: Habitat for Humanity, Apple Valley, 1998-2001 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Housing: VA–HUD Appropriations FY04, FY05, 2003-2005 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Housing: VA–HUD Appropriations FY04, FY05, 2003-2005 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Housing: VA–HUD Appropriations FY04, FY05, 2003-2005 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Housing: HUD Appropriations FY06, 2005 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Housing: HUD Appropriations FY06, 2005 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Housing: HUD Appropriations FY07, 2006 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Housing: HUD Appropriations FY07, 2006 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Housing: HUD Appropriations, San Bernardino, 2006-2007 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Housing: HUD Appropriations, Homelessness, 2007-2008 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Housing: HUD Appropriations, 2009, 2011 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Housing: Inland Temporary Homes, 2002-2006 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Housing: Neighborhood Initiative Program, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Hulda Crooks, 1986 (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - Hulda Crooks, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Immigration: Carol Lam, 2007 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Immigration: LA District INS Office, 1994-1997 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Immigration: LA District INS Office, 1997-1998 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Inyo County, 2000-2002 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - KVCR Television Station, 2006 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Labor, HHS, Education Subcommittee: Aerospace Workers, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Labor, HHS, Education Subcommittee: Appropriations FY01, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Labor, HHS, Education Subcommittee: Appropriations FY02, Lady B Ranch, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Labor, HHS, Education Subcommittee: Appropriations FY03–FY04, 2002-2004 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Labor, HHS, Education Subcommittee: Appropriations FY05, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Labor, HHS, Education Subcommittee: Appropriations FY06, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Labor, HHS, Education Subcommittee: Appropriations FY07, 2006 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Labor, HHS, Education Subcommittee: Appropriations FY11, 2010 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Labor, HHS, Education Subcommittee: Education Requests FY07, 2006 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Labor, HHS, Education Subcommittee: Education Requests FY08, 2007 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Labor, HHS, Education Subcommittee: Education Requests FY10, 2009 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Labor, HHS, Education Subcommittee: Lewis Center for Educational Research, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Labor, HHS, Education Subcommittee: Job Training Partnership Act, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Labor, HHS, Education Subcommittee: Job Training Partnership Act, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Labor, HHS, Education Subcommittee: Workers' Compensation, CPI, 1992, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Adventure Pass Recreation Fee, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Angeles National Forest, Land Exchange, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Army Corps of Engineers Hearing, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Bark Beetles, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Bark Beetles, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Bark Beetles, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Bark Beetles, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Big Bear Land Swap, 2008 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Brubaker–Mann Mine, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Boxer Wilderness Preservation Bill, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Cadiz Groundwater Storage Program, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Cadiz Valley Water Projects, 1995, 2006-2007 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Caffee Mine, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: California Desert Conservation Area Plan, Record of Division, 2006 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Crest Park, 1999-2002 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Death Valley Land Exchange, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Desert Acquisitions, Feinstein Meeting, 1998-1999 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Desert Acquisitions, 1998-1999 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Desert Acquisitions, Wildlands Conservancy, 1998-1999 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Desert Acquisitions, Wildlands Conservancy, 1998-1999 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Desert Conservation, 2009 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Energy, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Energy and Water Appropriations Requests FY03, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Energy and Water Appropriations Requests FY04, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Energy and Water Appropriations Requests FY05, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Energy and Water Appropriations Requests FY06, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Energy and Water Appropriations Requests FY06, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Energy and Water Development Appropriations Bill FY08, 2007 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Energy and Water Requests FY05, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Environment, Forestry, and Water, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Environment, Perchlorate, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Environment, Radon, 2001-2002 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Environmental Appropriations, San Bernardino, Inyo, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Environment, Water, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: FEMA, Flood Control, 1997-1998 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Forestry, Miscellaneous, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Fort Irwin Expansion, 1999-2003 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Fort Irwin Expansion, 1999-2003 (Box 25, Folder 15)